

#### **NGUYEN VAN NHAN**

**Date of Birth:** 1995-10-08

Phone: 0799833537

Email: nguyenvannhan0810@gmail.com

Address: Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh

Website: nvnhan0810.com

## **SUMMARY**

My major is Information Technology Engineer at Ho Chi Minh University of Technology and Education.

I have more than 4 years of experience with PHP Developers and related technology.

I desire to apply the knowledge and experience I have to serve the company, contribute to its development, and also affirm, and improve my value.

## **EDUCATION**

# Ho Chi Minh University of Technology and Education (HCMUTE)

Aug 2013 – Mar 2018

Major: Information Technology Engineer

GPA: 7.68

## WORK EXPERIENCE

ZIGExN VeNtura Dec 2022 - June 2024

- Build website and mobile app about franchising
- Manage and optimize system on GCP.
- Research and suggestion solution to improve system.
- Review code, support and training internship.
- Support other projects and teams related technology.

## **CMC Global Co.,LTD**

Jan 2022 - Nov 2022

- Optimize and maintain the Gym Management System of the customer.
- Developing a new system for the customer.

### **Poste Vietnam Company**

Aug 2021 - Dec 2021

- Develop Delivery Mobile App.
- Optimize the news websites and management system of the company.
- Building CI/CD system for the company using Jenkins.

## Vitalify Asia Co.,LTD

Nov 2020 - July 2021

- Develop and optimize projects of customers from Japan.
- Join to estimate, and analyze requirements of customers.

## Poste Vietnam Company

**Aug 2017 – Aug 2020** 

- Develop and maintain news websites.
- Develop a sale management system for the company.

## **SKILL**

| PHP - Laravel | 4/5 | Javascript             | 4/5 |
|---------------|-----|------------------------|-----|
| HTML5 - CSS3  | 4/5 | VueJS - Nuxt Framework | 3/5 |
| MySQL         | 4/5 | ReactJS                | 3/5 |
| Linux         | 3/5 | Docker - AWS - GCloud  | 2/5 |

## **PROJECTS**

#### Franchising system in Japan

- Build CMS for info managemen with Laravel and InertiaJS (React)
- Build Mobile App for user with Flutter.
- Setup GCP Serverless and CI/CD with services: Cloud Build, Cloud Run,...
- Use Twilio Conversations API for chatting feature, Twilio webhook for collecting data.

#### Gym system in Japan

- Make a management system for admin manager manage device, the crowdedness status
  of gym store.
- Make API for mobile application, gymers can use it to check-in, check-out or use services of gym.
- Using Laravel 7.x and Laravel 9.x for Web application and API. NodeJS to communication between IoT devices and API, Mobile app via AWS IoT.

Using Jenkins for CI/CD and AWS for infrastructure.

#### **Healthcare Application**

- Using ReactJs for Frontend and Laravel 6.x to make API.
- Using Pusher and Quickblox for real-time chat and notification, and AWS Lamda for scheduling tasks.

#### **Poste News Websites:**

- News websites supply information about Vietnam, Cambodia, and Myanmar for the
   Japanese Community who live or travel in there.
- Using Laravel Framework, Bootstrap 4, and Jquery.

#### **Delivery Website**

- This is a website supplying delivery information about restaurants in Ho Chi Minh, Da
   Nang, and Hanoi City.
- Using Nuxt Framework for Frontend and Laravel For Backend.

#### **Licenses and Sale Management**

- This is a system to manage the status of licenses, also the sale information of application.
- Using Laravel 7.x to make API with Laravel Sanctum for authorization.
- Using VueJS 2.x for Front-End side.

#### **Telesales Management Website**

- This is the website to store telesales data of an English Homestay.
- Using Laravel 7.x and Admin-LTE template for front-end.
- Git repo: https://gitlab.com/nguyenvannhan/thuan-homestay

## **LANGUAGE**

## **INTERESTS / HOBBIES**

- Second Language: English.
- Reading and comprehending English well.
- Can communicate basically in English.
- Play sports like Soccer, Badminton,
  - Jogging, etc
- Listen to music, and watch movies.